(My Precious Friend)
Nice to meet you all.
It's been a while, Sung Hwan. We all missed you.
Have you been well?
Yes. My gosh. I had no idea that I had the support...
of so many people.
Thanks to everyone's support and consolation,
I was able to send off Kkotbun the best way I could.
She remains...
a good memory in my heart too.
Pet loss syndrome sneaks up on you out of the blue.
- Right. - It will sneak up on you.
So call me when you feel down.
Right now, I feel emotional...
- at least once a day. - Of course.
- It's getting better now. - It will get better from here.
- It's getting better. - I see.
We're going to start the Rainbow Live.
It's been a while since we last had a big project.
It's the IRF Episode after four months.
Introducing the Rainbow Friends.
Today's episode will be IRF by Ku.
- By Ku. - By Ku.
That would be me.
This friend of mine knows how to enjoy life.
- He enjoys life. - Yes.
And our personalities match well.
I thought he was the perfect guy for our show.
- So I invited him. - Really?
He's the star of the fourth IRF Episode.
He's a friend of Sung Hwan. Bae In Hyuk, please come on out.
(Member Bae In Hyuk)
This feels weird.
- Hello. - My gosh.
He's handsome.
Hello.
(His character's narrative with Kim Hye Soo garnered attention.)
(Even alongside amazing actors and actresses,)
(his presence still shines.)
(They met each other in a drama and became close friends.)
(With his wide range performances,)
(he has won all kinds of acting awards.)
(Actor Bae In Hyuk)
Hey, Seon Tae Hyung.
(Hugging)
- Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
In Hyuk, could you say hello to our viewers?
Hello, everyone.
I'm doing my best to be a good actor.
My name is Bae In Hyuk.
- All right. - Hello.
(Nice to meet you.)
- You seem quite nervous today. - I'm very nervous.
You balled up your fists. That means you're nervous.
(Clenching)
This is your first time on our show.
How does it feel to be on our show for the first time?
I was quite excited to come here.
When I had just made my debut,
I was asked to pick a variety show I wanted to star on the most.
I picked I Live Alone then.
I'm so happy to be on the show and nervous at the same time.
Just pretend it's just you and me here.
- That's not good. - I don't think I should.
Let's check out...
the day-to-day life of Sung Hwan's friend, In Hyuk.
(Let's check out the day-to-day life of Sung Hwan's friend, In Hyuk.)
(The Tenacious Man)
"The Tenacious Man."
(Sunlight pours into the bedroom.)
(In Hyuk is sleeping without the blackout curtains.)
(Wriggling)
(Sunlight wakes him up, not the alarm.)
Not a lot of people can wake up...
- without the alarm these days. - Totally.
Hello. I've been living alone for 13 years.
I'm Actor Bae In Hyuk.
First of all, his name sounds handsome. Right?
"Bae In Hyuk."
- My father named me. - That's a handsome name.
You've been living alone for 13 years.
You must be... I thought you were in your 20s.
- I am. - What?
Were you in high school then?
- What? - I was in tenth grade by then.
Why? Did you run away from home when you were in high school?
- Maybe, it was for his dream. - I...
I dreamed of becoming an actor since middle school.
I got accepted into an arts high school.
Then I told my parents I was going to move out.
- Where did you stay at first? - I stayed in a goshiwon.
- Really? - After moving to Seoul,
I always lived in a one-bedroom studio.
- Then my career began to take off. - Really?
Now, I live in...
Your parents didn't help you at all? You moved there all on your own?
All on your own from the goshiwon?
Yes, ever since my second attempt at getting into university.
You graduated from university and fulfilled your military service?
- I did graduate, but... - Yes.
- You haven't served yet? - I have to.
- Not yet? - No, I have to.
You haven't served yet.
Why are you gloating?
- I should fulfill my military duty. - I envy you.
(As his body feels heavy with fatigue, he struggles to wake up.)
(Grunting)
(Grabbing)
(He makes the bed right after getting up.)
(Current time, 9:05am)
My face is so puffy.
(He comes out to the living room with a puffy face.)
- Gosh, it's so clean. - His house looks clean.
(Welcome to In Hyuk's clean house.)
In Hyuk and I have a few things in common.
- We both keep our house clean. - Right.
(The living room is decorated in neat beige tones.)
(The kitchen is right next to the living room.)
(Everything is organized with precision.)
- Gosh, they're perfectly organized. - He always keeps them organized.
(His clothes take up an entire room.)
Look. He organized them by color.
He arranged them by color.
He put white T-shirts together.
He's good at organizing his wardrobe.
- You like soccer. - Yes. I like K League.
- You're a fan of Jeonbuk FC. - Yes.
I thought placing my favorite items in my line of sight...
would make me happier and feel more comfortable at home.
So I placed items relevant to my hobbies and things I liked...
around the house.
I like displaying my favorite bottles of cologne.
I also like pizza.
You like pizza to the point that you have pizza keyrings?
Even your T-shirt?
- What does it say? "Eat pizza?" - Yes.
Looking at these items, he must really love pizza.
- How much do you like pizza? - Pizza...
How much do you have to like pizza to own these pizza-related items?
Pepperoni pizza is my favorite.
- Really? - That's my go-to pizza.
You eat all kinds.
I do eat all kinds.
(I love all kinds of pizza.)
(He trudges out in a unique pizza T-shirt.)
- Pepperoni pizza. - He's an oddball too.
- He's something else. Pizza... - You're such an oddball.
Why is it raining?
(Sliding it open)
(It's raining outside the window.)
What a nice view.
In Hyuk, your house has a nice view.
(Despite the rain, opening the window to ventilate the house)
(Grabbing)
(Clicking)
(He lights a candle after opening the window.)
You opened the window even when it was raining.
When I wake up, I always have to ventilate the house.
Even if raindrops get in?
- That's a good habit. - I have weak bronchial tubes.
I have to open the window to ventilate, no matter what.
And I always light candles because I'm sensitive to smells.
You have weak bronchial tubes.
- Why light candles? - Candles...
- That's... - So I open the window.
Listen. You opened the window...
- to ventilate the house. - Yes.
- Why light a candle? - Because of the smell.
- The flame will go out. - No, it won't.
Candles aren't good for bronchial tubes.
- They're not... - So I opened the window.
What on earth is he saying?
(What on earth is he saying?)
I'm very sensitive to smells.
- His house always smells great. - I hate to give off...
- the smell of a bachelor. - The musty smell?
So I pay attention to that.
(In Hyuk stubbornly goes around his house to light the candles.)
- It's fine with the windows open. - Right.
I always keep windows open too.
Gosh, I'm tired.
(Going around to open the windows tires him out.)
(Three candles including the one in the bedroom)
- You light a lot of candles. - That's a lot of candles.
(He opens the window in the bedroom as expected.)
Gosh, it's cold.
- You must not grill fish at home. - Never.
- I... - Never.
He'd hate it.
(He manages the smell of his house with scented candles.)
(He walks over to the kitchen again.)
His kitchen is so neat.
I tried my best to keep the house the way it was...
- when I moved in. - Of course.
Coffee...
(He's going to drink iced coffee to fully wake up.)
(Opening up)
(In Hyuk filled the pill organizer in advance.)
My gosh. You're in your 20s. You take that many supplements?
(Transferring)
(He swallows seven pills on an empty stomach.)
Seven pills on an empty stomach?
(He's amazing.)
Olive.
- Olive oil? - Yes.
(He continues to take health supplements.)
- There's more? - He takes a lot of supplements.
(He takes eight supplements just in the morning.)
You take a lot of supplements.
That tastes awful.
(That tastes awful.)
(He grabs a plastic bag after taking care of his health.)
- You throw it out right away. - Yes.
I don't have a trash can at home.
What? Really?
- You only use trash bags. - Right, just the trash bags.
You don't have trash cans...
- in case they smell, right? - Right.
I should throw out my trash cans too.
You're so simple.
(Joking)
- He'll throw out the ones he has? - That's pretty cool.
(Hanging the trash bag on a hook)
- That's hip. - It is hip.
- Hanging the trash bag... - I'll throw out mine today.
(He sits down for the first time today.)
(Liked Music)
(He picks "One Late Night in 1994.")
- The song by Jang Hye Jin? - "Sing Again 4."
(He drinks a sip of the coffee while listening to an old song.)
(He enjoys the retro vibe without moving an inch.)
(He calmly listens to the song.)
How much I love you
I prefer older songs. They're more my style.
He and I have similar tastes.
- You know, he's young. - Right.
But he only listens to old songs at the shoot.
We bonded over old songs.
- Lee Moon Sae's songs... - Right.
- The songs from the 90s? - Yes. He likes songs...
from the 80s and 90s.
- They have the best lyrics. - Right.
- Really? - They're like poems.
He's very sentimental.
When I listen to old songs, they sound different...
based on my mood.
(He picks a song that doesn't match his age.)
(Without doing anything)
(Staying perfectly calm)
(Staring out the window)
(Clicking)
- What's this sound? - What is that?
(A mysterious sound breaks the silence.)
(A keyboard?)
That's a keycap keyring.
It feels good to press on it.
When I listen to the clicking sound, it makes me feel at ease.
It helps me zone out too.
Keycap keyrings are popular among Gen MZ.
- Oh, that? - It's a trend?
- Yes. - Why do they do that?
How come you don't know about it?
I see. You end trends.
Don't get them.
- You'll end the trend again! - The trend is gone now.
(The keycap keyring trend will be over soon.)
- Hyun Moo, you gave me a DCC. - Yes.
There are piles of them at cafes now.
- Guess the messages I get now. - What?
They want me to eat butter tteok.
It keeps trending. So they want me to end it.
I finally realized the power you had.
(He plays with the trendy keyring while listening to an old song.)
(Clicking)
- That looks interesting. - It feels good to press the keys.
- Right. - Yes.
(Clicking)
(He starts pressing on the keys more absentmindedly.)
You get to do that a lot when you become an admin clerk.
Okay.
(You can do that throughout your military service.)
- You can listen to it over an hour. - My gosh. That's crazy.
- Thank you for the recommendation. - Seriously.
- You'd be sad to get discharged. - Thank you for the recommendation.
On top of that, all the admin clerks use the same kind of keyboard.
- Right. - Yes.
- They make that clicking sound. - I'm getting quite thirsty today.
(Practicing hard to become an admin clerk in the future)
(Getting up)
(Let me see.)
Ice cream?
- Frozen corn? - Frozen corn?
Corn tastes so good.
I love corn.
(I'll defrost it and eat it.)
(Observing)
- I always wait for it too. - You have to keep watching.
- Everyone must do it. - Yes.
I love watching the microwave.
- That's... - Zoning out at the microwave.
But don't they create electromagnetic waves?
Back in the day, people said we'd get dumb if we stared at them.
- Right. - Moms would tell us not to watch.
- Right. - That's why I take vitamins.
Gosh, why isn't it getting defrosted?
(Slamming)
(He's defrosting it only for 30 seconds.)
(Yawning)
(Opening it up)
(He repeatedly checks on it, unable to wait 30 seconds.)
- You're checking on it too often. - Just run it for three minutes.
- Gosh, he's so frustrating. - The thing is,
some parts are warm, and some parts are cold.
- Right. - So I kept running the microwave.
(After repeatedly opening and closing the microwave,)
(he finally gets a warm corn.)
(He excitedly comes back to the table.)
It's hot.
That looks so good.
(Blowing on it)
(He carefully has a bite as it's hot.)
(He's calm when he eats.)
(Munching)
(His morning has been chaotic.)
(Munching on the corn absentmindedly)
(Spacing out)
(I should stop eating.)
(He drinks up the coffee too.)
You don't watch TV or aren't on your phone.
- Right. - I don't like...
being on my phone.
Right.
His nickname is Oldie Bae.
- Oldie Bae. - Like an elder?
- Like an elder. - Oldie Bae.
- His last name... - I see.
I think I'm the ultimate zoomer.
- Your saying so makes you an oldie. - Really?
You also consider yourself young, Hyun Moo.
I'm the definition of Gen MZ.
- The definition of Gen MZ. - The definition of Gen MZ?
My nickname is Oldie MZ.
- Gen MZ. - Really? I thought I was a zoomer.
- The thing is... - He's just like me.
I noticed that he liked rice cakes when we were filming.
- He likes corn. - Right.
But he's not an oldie. Kids these days love them.
- Really? - That's right.
- See? I'm a zoomer. - Kids these days love...
black sesame flavors and corn.
It's called halmae-nial.
- Halmae-nial? - Kids like what grannies like.
So you knew.
- OC. - Halmae-nial.
"OC?"
- I know that one. "Of course." - "OC."
You're SEing.
- You're SEing. - SE.
- You're indeed Oldie Bae. - You're SEing.
- "Shortening everything." - You used a 20-year-old term.
I can't believe you said that.
What should I do today?
(Oldie Bae is full of worry.)
(Gulping it down)
(He washes the cup immediately.)
I love how clean he keeps his house.
(Squeaky clean)
In Hyuk's cup.
(The next one is In Hyuk's cup.)
(He washes his cup thoroughly.)
Gosh, it's cold.
(He starts washing his face in the middle of washing dishes.)
- He's just Kian84. - He's just like me.
People become successful for a reason.
He's already acting like a superstar.
(I can feel the energy of a superstar from him.)
(The promising superstar finishes washing everything.)
(Great)
Let's get changed now.
Let's go.
(He finishes getting changed.)
I guess he's going out.
(He puts on a jacket.)
- He looks like a college kid. - Right. He has that vibe.
I look cute.
I guess you like to look cute.
- That's what I strive for. - You strive to look cute.
A lot of people tell me that I look older than my age.
- Oldie Bae. - Yes.
- You look cute. - Yes.
- How cute. - Right?
Let's go.
(He goes out feeling satisfied.)
Gosh, I'm hungry.
Jjageuli, cheonggukjang stew,
budae jjigae...
What's going on?
I wonder...
if she's wearing purple eye makeup again.
Who are you talking to?
- That's what middle-aged men do. - Yes.
Oldies talk to themselves often.
(He arrives at a place while talking to himself.)
(Grilled Pork Belly)
- Hello. - Gosh.
(A local restaurant?)
- Am I the first customer? - I can tell the food will be good.
- Right. I can tell. - I bet the food is great.
It's my favorite restaurant.
You look a little thin.
Gosh, look at her.
- The eye makeup. - Right.
She's wearing the purple eye makeup.
- She's so cute. - Right.
She's such a charming lady.
She's so adorable.
(After saying hello to the lady with a unique charm...)
(Let me pick my dish.)
- Ma'am. - Yes.
- Your jjageuli is the best here. - Have some rice too.
I'm craving cheonggukjang stew too. I don't know what to do.
Get cheonggukjang stew then.
Should I get cheonggukjang stew?
- That's a great dish. - It's so delicious.
(Getting up)
Thank you.
(He grabs whatever he needs.)
It smells great.
(Like a regular customer, he knows what to do.)
(As he sets the table just like any other day...)
Thank you.
- Is this shepherd's purse? - Yes.
(Correct)
She's got great side dishes.
Hold on. Let me make it look pretty.
(Staring)
That looks so good.
- Come visit my neighborhood. - Yes.
Actually,
when I was a kid,
my grandma's cheonggukjang stew...
would cure my cold completely.
I love cheonggukjang stew.
(Let me start eating now.)
It's shepherd's purse.
It's spring. He ought to have some.
(Putting it in his mouth)
(Humming)
I love its scent.
In Hyuk always eats his food with gusto.
(Satisfied)
Gosh, I'm hungry.
(This time, he will finally have cheonggukjang stew.)
At last.
- Cheonggukjang stew? - That looks so good.
(Putting it in his mouth)
- Is it hot? - It must be hot.
(Grunting)
When I had the tofu, it burned my chest. You know what I mean?
- Gosh, I do. - Right?
(He has another spoonful despite the burning sensation.)
That must be too hot.
(Gosh, this cheonggukjang stew is really hot.)
- It's boiling. - Yes.
Gosh, isn't that too hot?
It's hot.
(But it's so good.)
- It hits the spot when it's hot. - Right, it does.
(He slurps more broth right away.)
Stew must always be burning hot.
(Frowning)
To be honest, I burned the roof of my mouth.
I ate in an excited state even though it was hot.
-The blisters should come off. - That's right.
- The skin should peel it right off. - You could push it gently.
- Yes. - The roof should be remodeled.
It should be remodeled?
I'm sweating.
(He sweats as he eats soup that's hot enough...)
(to remodel the roof of his mouth.)
(He drinks the soup until it's completely gone.)
It was a good meal.
(He perfectly cleared the meal with cheonggukjang stew.)
Ma'am, I'd like to pay.
- I really enjoyed the meal. - Thank you.
Thank you, Ma'am.
- Thank you. - All right.
- Was it okay? - Yes, it was so tasty.
- Really? - Yes.
Did you season shepherd's purse with doenjang?
Yes, I seasoned it with doenjang.
- Regular doenjang? - Yes.
- I want to see Ma'am again. - I know.
- You should visit. - Yes.
- Thank you for the food. - Okay.
(He sets off after filling his stomach.)
I enjoyed it even more because it was raining.
(He heads over to somewhere.)
(Opening)
(He returns and gets into the car.)
All right. Let's go.
(He starts driving somewhere.)
(All of this will seem like an excuse to you)
(He sings to the rhythm.)
("BK Love" by MC Sniper)
He likes old songs.
It's time for the next song.
What is it?
Let's listen...
to "We Were in Love" by Ko Kyoung Pyo.
You might think that the lyrics are beautiful, but it isn't true.
What are you doing?
- Why is he hosting? - He's suddenly hosting.
(Laughing)
You're a radio DJ and a singer.
(Still)
(I love you)
Still, I love you
- What was that? - What?
(Squeezing his eyes shut)
I don't know what to do.
Still
(He's still absorbed in the song.)
Thank you. We've listened...
to "We Were in Love" by Ko Kyoung Pyo.
What's the next song?
Hey, are you hosting a radio show?
It's "Love and Remember" by god.
I haven't listened to it in a while.
(Vocalizing)
You!
(In Hyuk, you!)
- I'm in trouble. - My goodness.
We've listened...
to "Love and Remember" by god.
- Hello, everyone. - What?
- Hold on. What's this? - I'd like to thank...
everyone who came here...
- to listen to my song. - What's up with that tone?
The song title is "Little Doll,"
and my name is Bae In Hyuk.
- You even made it rhyme. - Today's weather is...
overcast and rainy.
You're in a hiking club, right?
You're totally a middle-aged man.
- I'm sweating. - You're totally a middle-aged man.
What was that? I wondered what you were doing.
Your car looks like a Galloper at this point.
(Hyun Moo takes it further.)
- I know. - Right? He has that vibe.
There isn't a hint of hipness.
His car suddenly looks tacky.
(Joking)
I know the latest songs too.
Which ones do you know?
Well, there are many songs.
- Okay. - Like what?
SISTAR?
(SISTAR?)
(Let's push, push to the south.)
(Music doesn't stop as he drives to his destination.)
"I was thinking the same thing."
- "'Cause, like..." - Oh, my.
(He switches to a song from an animated movie.)
(Love is an open)
(Door)
This is driving me crazy.
(Fate in time)
(He even pulls off a trot song.)
(Satisfied)
My goodness.
(My goodness,)
(In Hyuk)
(To my side)
(Voice cracking)
(You'll come back)
Now, we're listening to a musical number.
(He moves on to a musical number.)
(Spreading his arm)
He really seems like a dad.
(Gulping)
(Vocalizing)
Let's go.
(In Hyuk, let's go!)
That's a must.
(Vocalizing)
(Voice cracking)
(He wraps it up in his own way.)
(Oh, no.)
That's too bad.
I really enjoy singing.
- Of course. - It's fun to sing.
Everyone does that in their car.
- That's right. - They do, right?
- That's the fun of driving. - Everyone is the same.
- You sing the notes you can't hit. - Of course.
- Yes. - When the radio is on,
you answer the DJ's questions at times.
I answer...
- and act out a skit. - I do that.
It's boring to sing only.
You need to make comments too. "Hey."
- That's right. - That's right.
(Sighing)
My throat wasn't warmed up that day.
- Had my throat been warmed up... - Would it have been insane?
The musical scene would've been...
- It would've been in danger. - Seriously.
("I Will Give You All," "BK Love," "Destiny," "Love Always Run Away,")
("We Were in Love," "Love and Remember,")
("Little Doll," "In the Shade of a Street Tree,")
(Love Is an Open Door," "This Is the Moment," etc.)
(He sang a total of 27 songs.)
Twenty-seven songs?
He had a concert.
(In Hyuk's concert takes it far.)
(He stops singing and becomes nervous.)
Why is he suddenly nervous?
- This is bad. - Did he make a wrong turn?
It happens when you sing.
(His face hardens.)
Oh, my. What's wrong?
Is it because of coffee? I want to pee.
(Oh, no.)
It's because you sang from your stomach.
(Feeling bad)
(The next service area is 21km away.)
It's about to burst.
(It's about to burst.)
Why are you drinking more coffee when you want to pee?
What is he going to do?
(His dignity is on the line with this "Pee and Furious.")
It's about to burst.
(His bladder is about to burst.)
Why are you drinking more coffee when you want to pee?
What is he going to do?
(In Hyuk, you need to hold it in!)
(Breathing out)
- I need to focus on something else. - Right. Think about something else.
- It's hard to believe - This is insane.
It wasn't easy.
Seven kilometers.
Five kilometers.
Two kilometers.
Hurry!
Gosh, that bump...
(He exits the car hurriedly because he can barely hold it in.)
(Rushing over)
I really need to pee!
Why is it so far?
Oh, no. Hurry!
Thank goodness.
(He arrives at the men's toilet.)
(He lets go of his worries.)
- Is the problem fixed? - It's fixed.
- He looks happy. - He's happy. It's nice.
- He got his color back. - His face became a bit pale.
(With lighter body,)
(he hits the road again.)
Oh, my gosh. Is that "Honey" by Park Jin Young?
Part Two has begun.
For how many hours did you sing?
Aside from the intermission, about three hours.
- The intermission? - The intermission?
- Was there an intermission? - I stopped at the service area.
- Just now... - I see.
(My visit to the service area was the intermission.)
(He sings a ballad song for Part 2 of the concert.)
(After overcoming the crisis of needing to use the toilet,)
(he becomes absorbed in his performance on the road.)
What am I going to do?
- Things are getting worse. - No, it's good.
Gosh, look at the fog. Seriously.
I can't see anything.
(The visibility becomes low.)
My goodness. It's like a horror movie.
- Do you know the movie, "The Mist?" - Yes.
I'm reminded of "The Mist."
I feel like I'm entering a different world.
It's really scary.
It was my first time seeing such thick fog.
(He enters a narrow alley in the thick fog.)
I can't see.
(He manages to arrive at a place.)
What's up with this fog?
(He becomes flustered.)
It really looks like a horror movie.
It's so cold.
(Walking over)
What is this place?
(He opens the door without hesitation.)
I'm in Sunchang.
It's a country home that's used...
by my parents, me, my younger brother, and my grandma.
My mom lived two houses down...
when she was little.
- That's incredible. - My grandpa's tomb is nearby,
so I naturally come here often.
(A cozy place for the family)
My family meets there often.
I want to go there.
- You should come. - It looks cozy.
(There is a garden behind the house.)
We visit every weekend for gardening.
- Every weekend? - Yes.
- It's corn. - Right. It looks nice.
(They've grown various crops.)
We give the crops to our acquaintances.
It's very fun to do that.
Gosh, it's cold.
It's really cold in the country home.
Let's have a cup of coffee.
(Let's warm myself up with a cup of coffee.)
(Taking off)
(Rummaging)
No way.
(He finds his mom's fur vest.)
- A fur vest. - That vest is really warm.
- It's really warm. - It's the best.
Gosh, it's small.
(I'll just wear it since it's cold.)
(He wears his jumper over the vest for warmth.)
(Satisfied)
I should go outside since I'm here.
(Now that I'm bundled up, it's time to go outside.)
(He takes a chair outside.)
(He sits in the pavilion in front of the house.)
It's nice.
(Drinking)
It's like a commercial.
- He looks cool. - He looks nice,
as if a filter is on.
That's good to hear.
This is nice.
(Satisfied)
(He enjoys his moment in the natural filter.)
My goodness.
It'll be so scary to run into a fog like that.
(The foggy view with the blurry shapes is scary.)
I feel like Ja Yeon will come out saying, "You're here."
Ja Yeon?
I can't see the mountains at all.
If you look out from the yard,
the house is surrounded by mountains.
It's very beautiful.
- My goodness. - Isn't it beautiful?
It's beautiful.
That's how it normally looks.
- It's beautiful. - The sun sets beautifully.
It's scary.
(Thick fog took the life out of the place.)
I felt like I was in a different world.
Every time I visit, I see different charms of the house.
Gosh, what's that sound?
(Barking)
This is nice.
What's nice?
Gosh, it's cold. I should get to work.
What?
What work?
Gosh, I'm exhausted.
(He walks over to a place, looking strange.)
(Hold on.)
It should be at a place like this.
(There's no one around in the foggy place.)
- It's really scary. - I know.
It's atmospheric.
(Plowing)
Where are you?
He looks so suspicious.
For goodness' sake. Why is it dead already?
Whom did he kill?
(Eyes wide open)
(With his eyes wide open, he continues to plow.)
Oh, my. He looks so scary.
(He digs something out.)
What is it?
A sprout?
I personally love shepherd's purse.
Shepherd's purse hides here and there.
When I dig up shepherd's purse...
I don't know if I feel that way since it's my own work,
but it tastes much more tender.
So I dug up shepherd's purse diligently...
in order to make doenjang jjigae.
You can find an entire group when there's one.
(You can find an entire group when there's one.)
(He collects shepherd's purse amidst similar-looking grass.)
How fascinating.
Gosh, the root got cut off.
- The root has all the nutrients. - It looks like moss.
You wouldn't recognize it if you hadn't dug it up before.
- You've done it since childhood. - That's right.
- Yes. - That's why you can spot it.
- I see. - My grandma raised me.
So I naturally had such experiences.
(He goes in search of the next shepherd's purse.)
The first characteristic is...
that it's really close to the ground.
The leaves stick to the ground.
That's one characteristic.
The most confusing thing is that there's one similar-looking weed.
I don't know what that weed is.
But the back side of that weed is white.
If the back side is white, it isn't shepherd's purse.
That's the difference.
You're right. I see what you mean.
That weed doesn't stick to the ground.
The leaves point upward.
(Unlike shepherd's purse, its leaves point upward.)
Lastly, shepherd's purse is never alone.
Is it with someone?
When you find one shepherd's purse,
you'll find its friends nearby.
- They live as a group. - Yes.
Shepherd's purse has such characteristics.
There are so many.
He's like Little Tiger.
- You're right. - He has that side.
- He's the male version. - What is it?
It looks fun.
It's therapeutic.
- I bet. It's therapeutic to watch. - It's so big.
(Digging up shepherd's purse gives him a therapeutic moment.)
His snot looks like dew.
(Dangling)
I can't believe you spotted it.
- It looks fine since it's clear. - It's very clear.
- Thank goodness. - Usually, it's sticky.
I've never seen a man with such clear snot.
- That's right. - It doesn't look very dirty.
- I'm glad. - It doesn't look very dirty.
- It's like dew. - It almost looks like sweat.
(In Hyuk's snot can't be clearer.)
Let's go.
(Groaning)
(Aching)
You look a bit tired.
It was exhausting indeed.
I put too much effort into the concert.
Fate in time
It's natural to be exhausted after the concert.
That's right. It was after the concert.
- It's still therapeutic, right? - It's very therapeutic.
(Sniffling)
It's enough.
He dug up a lot.
You can season it or add it to doenjang jjigae.
(Upon return, he enters the garden inside the yard.)
There's so much to work on.
(Looking around)
This is goldmoss stonecrop.
What was that?
- Does it grow on stone? - It's my first time seeing that.
Goldmoss stonecrop has different names...
depending on the region.
It grows on damp ground.
Many restaurants serve seasoned goldmoss stonecrop.
It makes a nice side dish.
Among actors your age, you'd be the most knowledgeable about it.
- Seriously. - Right?
(He collects goldmoss stonecrop after collecting shepherd's purse.)
There's a lot.
(Picking)
So it grows in such places.
(He is busy collecting the goldmoss stonecrop.)
Oh, gosh! That surprised me!
Who is that?
Gosh, how long has it been to come here?
I know.
(Two people approach the house amidst the fog.)
Where is he?
(In Hyuk is busy collecting the goldmoss stonecrop.)
Oh, gosh! That surprised me!
Who is that?
Gosh, how long has it been to come here?
Who is Gong Yoo and who is Lee Dong Wook?
I don't think it will really matter.
Where is he?
There he is.
- I thought it was a bear. - Where's my friend?
- A bear? - Gosh!
- Bae In Hyuk! - Come out!
- What are you doing? - Why are you so late?
I'm collecting these for you guys.
Collect some more.
- Were you collecting them? - Are they his friends?
- Yes. - Your hometown friends?
My friends appeared as if they were in "Guardian."
They're my hometown friends.
In Jeonju,
we went to elementary, middle, and high school together.
We're still great friends to this day.
(Bae In Hyuk's friend, Jeon Chang Ok)
So this is Lee Dong Wook.
(Bae In Hyuk's friend, Kim Yang Won)
We were on the soccer team during middle school.
Whenever I had a performance in my arts high school,
they all came to watch as my close friends.
I'll quickly make...
shepherd's purse doenjang jjigae.
Weren't you straining yourself in those rubber boots?
(He quickly prepares dinner.)
Are they office workers?
They are self-employed. They run a meat restaurant.
- I see. - They're business partners.
- Really? - I see.
What about your father?
He's in Jeonju.
There will be some side dishes.
(He opens the fridge naturally.)
Take some of them.
I'll try to get this prepared quickly.
- Which ones? - There were a few side dishes.
- Let's take out the bean sprouts. - Take out a few of them.
The seaweed stems as well.
The bellflower roots?
(Enough is taken out for their meal.)
They're all setting everything up naturally.
We all eat together often at my family's house.
The meat must be of good quality.
Friends are the best.
Won't it take long to make the jjigae?
The jjigae won't take long.
(Meanwhile,)
(In Hyuk is washing the shepherd's purse he collected.)
Gosh, there's so much dirt.
There's a lot of dirt on the ends.
- Right. - They have to be washed thoroughly.
- They have to be washed a lot. - They have to be washed a lot.
- Right. - You might feel the dust.
(Washing over and over)
He's diligent.
(The dirt is removed after repeating it many times.)
There we go. This should be clean enough.
This much dirt is fine. We all grew up eating dirt.
That will bust up your appendix.
It feels like your cooking will be really good.
I cook fairly often.
The shepherd's purse doenjang jjigae is really easy.
The shepherd's purse is put into the pot.
A big spoonful and a half or two big spoonfuls are put in.
(And frying powder?)
Frying powder is added in.
What? In there?
Originally, when shepherd's purse doenjang jjigae is made,
I heard that rice water should be used to make it light and thick.
But adding in frying powder or flour...
makes it really light...
and it makes the texture feel thick.
That is why I use them.
I see.
Minced garlic brings up its flavor a lot more.
These are really spicy peppers.
I add the pepper and green onion...
to make the soup have a refreshing taste.
It's done once the tofu is added.
It's really easy, isn't it?
Gosh, shepherd's purse. It looks really good.
(The natural shepherd's purse doenjang jjigae is ready.)
As I have lived alone for a while, I got sick of food delivery.
(The cooking skills of the one who has lived alone for 13 years)
I make my own meals quite often.
- You're a great cook. - It looks delicious.
He throws everything in as he cooks.
- I can tell he's a great cook. - Can you tell?
Of course.
The second dish is the goldmoss stonecrop salad.
It can be made easily with some chojang...
to be a delicacy.
He's a great cook.
(Meanwhile, his friends are almost done with grilling the meat.)
- Gosh, it smells great. - The kimchi looks insane.
Gosh, that looks good!
Shepherd's purse doenjang jjigae.
(In Hyuk's vegetable dishes are served as well.)
(I'm hungry.)
You went through so much, In Hyuk.
(He takes a bite...)
(of the shepherd's purse doenjang jjigae first.)
(Satisfied)
(Groaning)
It's good, isn't it?
(He takes a bite and nods without saying anything.)
They really must be close friends.
- They won't talk. - They won't talk.
They won't even catch up with each other.
Close friends don't do that.
It won't be weird if they leave after finishing their meal.
- That can happen. - Without saying a word.
- They won't even say bye. - Right.
- One is missing after the meal. - Right.
The shepherd's purse tastes refreshing.
- Isn't it really soft? - Yes.
Our Jeonju friends came over to my place in Seoul.
Was the braised chicken better or is this better?
This.
This is way better. I'm serious.
Tofu and kimchi, potato jeon, and braised chicken.
We had many different things.
But this is the best for me.
- Right. - It's really good.
It's nice and refreshing.
I felt really proud as they really enjoyed it.
- Try some of this as well. - What is that?
- Did you make it a salad? - Yes.
(He picks up some of the goldmoss stonecrop salad.)
You've seen this in restaurants, right?
That must taste the best.
It's good.
(He eats freely with the positive response.)
(Chang Ok focuses on the shepherd's purse.)
(Groaning)
Can you pull out some more shepherd's purse?
- That would be hard, right? - I believe so.
(Eating)
- Eat slowly. - Right.
I have to lose weight.
(Eating)
I want to meet that guy.
He's just like you.
This is what he's like during a shoot.
"I'm on a diet."
"I'm going to have two eggs for lunch at the convenience store."
But during the shoot, he shoves in so much bread.
Right. He eats more snacks than his meals.
He follows a diet plan during mealtimes,
but he eats all he wants regularly.
Right. He follows a diet plan during mealtimes.
- Right. - He eats all he wants regularly.
People like him have less rice during mealtimes.
Is there more of the doenjang jjigae?
I'll get you some more. It'll be just the soup that's left.
Have my solid ingredients. I won't have them.
I'll give you some of mine.
(Taking)
- I feel proud. - It means it's really good...
- if his friends say that. - Right.
(They all start eating again without a word.)
It feels like these guys will really leave after eating.
After finishing their meal,
they will definitely lie around in the living room with the TV on.
- They won't say a word. - Right.
They probably wouldn't have watched his dramas as well.
They really don't watch my dramas. They say it's hard to watch them.
- Definitely. - It will feel really awkward.
It will feel awkward to be together and watch his dramas.
- It's an awkward situation. - Right.
We've seen each other ever since we were very young.
- That's how it is with old friends. - Right.
- I feel proud. - Right.
I don't really feel anything when other people say it's good.
- Right. - Really?
It means it's really good if Chang Ok says it's good.
As I started living alone at an early age,
I felt more precious feeling about my parents,
and I learned to respect them even more.
I had a dream of becoming an actor at a young age,
and I wanted to take responsibility in that.
I worked diligently with part-time jobs,
and tried my best with my social life.
Through many different experiences,
I became a lot more solid.
Because of that,
I was often told that I was mature.
That's perfect. They're watching soccer together.
(Today, he can enjoy his youth in his hometown.)
- There was a match that night. - That's perfect!
- Gosh! Please! - Oh, come on.
Oh, come on.
(Maturity Ripened in My Own Speed)
That was great!
After watching your drama,
I just thought you were a rising star these days.
But you're very charming.
- He's charming. - Right. He's charming.
- He's charming. - Right.
- Thank you. - We have a superstar judge with us.
Mr. 84.
(Deciding)
I thought that he was like the shepherd's purse.
- Gosh! - Gosh! That's amazing.
- It has long roots. - When boiled up well,
I believe we will be seeing another superstar.
The man who is like the shepherd's purse.
He was like the shepherd's purse.
- The more he gets boiled... - You're like the shepherd's purse.
- Me? - Yes.
It's because I'm a superstar.
I have a great feeling about him. I really enjoyed it.
He's full of charms.
- He's really charming. - Thank you.
That was great.
The weather is great these days, isn't it?
- The weather is much better now. - Right.
Have you come to enjoy spring?
I feel all over the place as I arrived yesterday.
- You're usually in New York. - Right.
I came back after visiting New York.
He came because of you.
- Did you really come because of me? - Yes.
I watched the trailer,
and you called out my name around 30 times.
He went too far with it.
(Hue!)
I tried my best to change.
Watch the clip and give me your assessment.
(Create Something From Moo)
(Create Hue From Moo)
- What? - "Create Hue From Moo."
Gosh, that's so annoying.
(Hyun Moo arrived somewhere early in the morning.)
Is it open?
It's 10:35am right now.
Where is this?
You will know as soon as you see it.
Early in the morning?
My eyes are going wild already. What do I do?
My eyes are going wild.
(The place Hyun Moo has visited)
The showroom. Has it opened?
This is the Nordic furniture store.
It's been a while since I saw there.
I went really often when I studied abroad.
You want to buy everything that is displayed there.
- Right. - Right.
(A large warehouse of products)
It's a pleasant feeling.
- It's fun to be there. - I love the showroom.
(DIY interior paradise)
Hue Park's interior design...
kept popping up in my head after visiting his house.
(As soon as he visited Hue's house...)
(Smiling)
(He naturally got attracted to Hue after a sweet start.)
(Even when Hue drank water...)
(Where is that cup from?)
(I like this vase.)
(This was just a few dollars.)
(None of the things I use are expensive.)
(Why don't my things look nice when they're expensive?)
The price didn't matter.
(After feeling the bitter taste of interior design...)
I kept wanting to change things...
and become more like him.
That was why I did a bit of research.
I thought that the brand or its fanciness...
was what was important, but that wasn't it.
"Simple is the best."
I want to find simple things that I won't get bored with...
and add my own colors to them.
Hue Park plus interior.
That becomes Hue-terior.
- That's my goal today. - Gosh!
(I got Hue)
I got Hue!
- I got Hue! - I got Hue!
- I got Hue! - Hue-terior.
This is the vibe Moo-KEA aims for.
A Nordic interior design expert with his own colors.
Today,
I will become Moo-KEA.
What was that?
I don't like things that feel excessive.
(Forget the Hyunmoo-terior that was full of excessiveness.)
I will find modern and simple things...
that I won't get bored with,
and slightly add my own colors to them.
He kept asking me where I bought my things.
- So he really went. - Right.
It's been a while since I felt inspired...
after visiting someone's house.
You always tend to steal things from others.
When someone's hobby or style looks nice,
- I copy it right away. - you copy it right away.
It's my first time seeing you copy something so politely.
- Right. - He's usually shameless about it.
- Right. - Really?
He acts as if it were already his.
I'm a toady.
I'm from the older generation.
(Hue got Hyun Moo's respect as he's a New Yorker.)
(He hunts for Hue items while being equipped with toadyism.)
"Hue items."
My eyes are going wild.
(Amazed)
Gosh.
(There are fascinating items displayed everywhere he goes.)
(After taking a few steps...)
Swedish restaurant.
Is the food good here?
A lot of people are here.
You're eating right away?
(He grabs the cart.)
(Food before Hue-terior)
This is how we get our food?
- The store opens at 11am. - Right.
The restaurant opens at 10:30am.
The idea is to eat before you start shopping.
A lot of walking is needed when shopping.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hi.
Everyone is out here so early.
Hello.
How adorable! Hello.
I bought the DCC ingredients...
after watching the show.
Really? Did you buy them because of me?
Why? Isn't the trend over?
- I wanted to try making them. - Did you make them?
- Everything must've been cheap. - Not yet.
- They're really hard to make. - I don't know how to make it yet.
- Buy the kadayif. Don't make it. - Right.
That will stress you out a lot.
I'll wrap them up with the plastic bags as well.
(That will stress you out a lot.)
What are you going to have?
The kimchi fried rice and the pork cutlet.
- Are those dishes good? - Yes.
(Interested)
The kimchi fried rice and the pork cutlet?
- I'll get the meatballs. - Right.
- The pork loin cutlet. - Right.
That's the most famous dish, right?
The pork cutlet is famous. The chicken steak is also popular.
- I'll get a chicken steak as well. - Right.
Please place the meatballs on top of the kimchi fried rice.
- I'll get the children's dish. - Why did you get everything?
I was told to get the drumstick.
(The drumstick sounds good as well.)
There aren't many drumsticks left! Gosh.
There aren't many drumsticks left!
The drumstick was recommended.
(He sweeps away all dishes without stopping.)
That looks delicious.
(He gets some mushroom soup as well.)
I must have some dessert.
Kouign-amann.
- One must have some dessert. - Isn't that too much food?
Gosh, I'm eating so much.
(Smiling)
What is this?
I'm not serving the food.
(The 3-tray cart appears.)
(He heads to the battlefield with confidence.)
- It feels like a horror movie. - Right.
It feels like "The Last Supper."
There are a lot more options now.
(The taster salmon salad and the recommended kimchi fried rice)
I must have the pork cutlet as it's a popular dish.
I must have this as this is an original dish.
I feel like a European.
(A perfect meal along with the dessert)
He must've been really hungry.
(Shall I give it a try?)
(Eating)
(He takes a big bite of the drumstick as well.)
It's good. Gosh, I should've brought more!
(It's good. Gosh, I should've brought more!)
- The drumstick looks good. - The drumstick was good.
(The pork cutlet is up next.)
(He adds kimchi to the kimchi fried rice right away.)
(Hyun Moo fills up his stomach before shopping.)
(He eats with both hands.)
He looks like a greedy king.
Gosh, I feel sleepy. I'm getting a blood sugar spike.
I felt so sleepy.
I should head home now. I feel sleepy.
Go inside and get some sleep.
Right.
Gosh, I feel full.
(Swiping)
Where's the interior design?
(Hyun Moo goes through Hue's social media page.)
Stop!
These vibes.
A rug.
(I must get vases!)
I must get vases!
These colors.
(After looking through his textbook...)
Is it a fabric sofa?
(Cramming for Hue-terior)
Right.
Simple lights that are in a white tone.
I have a long way to go. What do I do?
- Right. - When will I look for all of these?
You need to spare a whole day.
Lights, sofa, furniture...
It will be tough in a single day.
(He heads to the showroom after cleaning up his trays quickly.)
These are carried around, right?
(He picks up a shopping bag and gets ready to shop!)
This is Moo-KEA's plan. In my house,
(In my house)
the art room feels dead right now.
At one point, it became a storage room...
instead of a workroom.
After becoming a storage room, I didn't want to go in anymore.
But I sold my oven to Jae Hyeon...
and I sold my piano to Hue.
After securing some more space,
I wondered why I neglected this place.
I decided to make this a place I want to go inside again.
What must I do then?
I must use Hue-terior.
When you look at the workrooms of trendy artists,
the chairs, key items,
or tables look nice.
Nothing is over the top.
Everything is simple.
- Placed nonchalantly. - Right. Placed nonchalantly.
So chic and placed nonchalantly.
I wanted to make it look like...
a place an artist would wander around in.
I'm certain of the things I want today.
Chairs, tables, lights, and decorative items.
That's everything.
Chairs, tables, lights, and decorative items? That's everything.
I won't be buying other furniture.
Let's fill in the cart.
(Eyes opening wide)
The stores look the same...
- in any country. - Right.
There's a certain style.
It's like how McDonald's chains look the same everywhere.
- He's different indeed. - Now,
he's going to say the same thing wherever he goes.
"The stores look the same in any country."
It wasn't even a mind-blowing comment.
- Right. - He accepts it differently.
I noticed that you're a bit toady.
It's serious.
(Eyes glowing)
This chair can become a good-looking piece of trash.
It does look pretty.
Should I use it when I'm painting?
It's excessive from the start.
Do you think so?
Like this in front of the easel.
(He tries using it right away.)
It's not bad. I think I'll use it.
- It does look nice. - No.
The easel will be placed here.
This isn't bad.
It's a chair for children.
(It's a chair for children.)
Oh, like this?
The light is placed on it like this?
This looks nice.
- No. - It's so cute.
It's far away from your theme of being simple.
But there needs to be a key item.
It has to look simple first.
(Reacting)
I should pick this up on my way out.
I can't be carrying this around.
This looks nice.
But having one would look off.
It should be placed with the pink one.
What?
Is there a concept for workrooms?
A trendy workroom.
Workroom.
(Gosh, what is this?)
- What is this? - A cable?
What?
(Throwing the cable in the cart)
The color was so pretty.
- Why would you buy so many cables? - Why would you...
- Hyun Moo. - Who buys a cable...
because it's pretty?
We sold a whole bunch during the bazaar.
(We clearly sold them during the bazaar.)
(Since I sold them, I should get new ones.)
I'm certain of the things I want today.
Chairs, tables, lights, and decorative items.
That's a sort of decorative item.
I shouldn't get something like this.
This won't do.
(His plan failed miserably from the beginning.)
Goodness. I'm not here to get these.
(In the end, he nonchalantly added a charging adapter to the cart too.)
(Looking around)
A stool?
(Hyun Moo found the chair section.)
Gosh, these chairs...
(Colorful)
- There are so many pretty chairs. - They have many chairs.
This one has a really nice vibe.
(He strides up and takes a seat.)
Gosh, this chair... A rattan chair.
I can put something in here.
(Impressed)
What if I paint in this chair?
(What if I paint in this chair?)
The painting became the standard for buying furniture.
For the studio.
It's giving me goosebumps.
(What if this chair was in my studio?)
A true artist paints on the floor.
It'll give a nice vibe to my studio.
(Shopping cart: Rattan chair)
Where's the chair I saw on social media?
They don't have the chair that got a lot of attention.
(TSM is curious about the chair that got a lot of attention.)
Oh, here it is!
- It's there. - Right.
The green chair is really popular.
- It was really comfortable. - Gosh.
- It's pretty, right? - This one is the best.
This one's pretty.
This is it.
There must be another color too.
Oh, it's this one. The orange chair.
I'll use that chair for painting.
(Moosquiat faces a dilemma as a painter.)
What should I do?
They have it in this color too.
- What is this? - That's the latest item.
That chair in beige...
- was released for the first time. - Oh, really?
- It's in beige? - It is.
"New." I bet even G-DRAGON hasn't bought this yet.
He's getting it for sure.
You might as well...
- get the latest one. - Right?
Joy, you understand...
- as a maximalist. - I get you.
- That's right. - Since you were at it.
All right.
What is this?
What is this section?
- They have an art studio theme. - It's an art studio.
That showroom is a great reference for you, Hyun Moo.
Yes, this is a studio. This space is totally for me.
Oh, placing a rug like this for a natural vibe?
- That's nice too. - A vibe like this?
- It's nice, right? - For the studio.
It won't look weird even if I get paint on it.
It's the mindset of Moo-KEA.
Before, I'd just get one item and place it...
and said it was hip.
But now, I'd see what suits the item...
if I place it in a room.
I've developed a sense to see the overall theme.
I can now mix and match decor items.
I thought, "When I get something, let's get a proper one."
I'm definitely getting this.
(Shopping cart: Rattan chair, latest chair, rug)
There was a rug this big in the art studio-themed showroom.
Which one was it?
It's like the rug you'd see in a lockup cell Chunhyang is in.
The rug on the floor of Chunhyang's lockup cell.
(His description is like a riddle.)
It's Lohals.
- Yes, it's Lohals. - They understood him.
- They did. - How did they get you...
with that kind of description?
- It's... - Everyone feels the same way.
It's the straw mat for rolling up a dead body!
How did you get it after hearing that it's from Chunhyang's cell?
You're amazing.
(Hyun Moo goes to the section the staff told him.)
That's right. Chunhyang's prison cell.
This is it.
(He finally found the rug from Chunhyang's prison cell.)
"Chunhyang's prison cell."
Everyone gets it.
- For rolling up a body. - For rolling up a body.
For rolling up a body.
(Let's go home with me.)
I have that rug at home.
- Oh, he has the same one. - Really?
You should've told me.
(Hyun Moo is still browsing.)
I should get a few of Hue Park-style cups.
(Surprised)
(He found a Hue-style cup.)
(He saw the Hue-style cup at Hue's place last time.)
(Where is that cup from?)
(The cup cost five dollars.)
(It has a crazy nice vibe.)
(He wanted to buy all the items that Hue got with his sense.)
(Hue, I'm getting this cup because of you.)
- I only use that cup these days. - It's actually different from mine.
What?
- What? - It's different from the cup...
that you used.
I didn't get it from IKEA.
- Please share me a link. - All right.
(So I can get one again.)
Actually, I didn't buy that because it was trending.
I used that cup from an Italian brand...
for the first time when I was living in LA.
I remembered...
- that it had a nice feel. - It must have a story.
I do have one too. I saw it for the first time at his place.
- You loved that feel. - I loved that feel.
I can't forget...
- how it felt in my hand. - How it felt in your hand?
Compared to the cup I got...
- from IKEA, - He's driving me crazy.
Hue's cup is a bit wider.
- That's right. - This is how it feels in my hand.
What you're saying is right, though.
- You're actually right. - The way it feels in your hand...
You don't have to align with everything he says.
Hyun Moo...
It's this one.
Hue's lighting.
(I found Hue's lighting.)
- This is the one. - That's the one, right?
- Yes, I have that one too. - That's it. It's simple and nice.
It's pretty.
This is Hue's cup.
Wait, this is Hue's.
Hue Park. This is it.
I needed a vase anyway.
Don't they have Hue's fruit plate?
(He's getting more dizzy.)
Why do you keep adding his name to every item?
You must flinch every time he mentions your name.
It's my first time someone...
mentions my name this many times, so I'm flustered.
Doesn't it feel like a new kind of bullying?
I know.
- It looks really scary from here. - I mean,
it's scary for him.
(He pours out lots of affection for Hue.)
(Excuse me. I'm looking for Hue's items.)
Excuse me.
The one with a nice vibe like this.
It looks like this.
Where you can place apples, bananas, and Shine Muscat.
A plate this big. It looks like this.
(Do you have a plate that looks like this?)
It looks like this.
It's like a charade.
- That's not the one. - That's a different one.
They didn't have it.
This feel is a bit...
It's a bit...
I should just get this, then.
This doesn't give off that feel.
(Bitterly getting the plate that doesn't have Hue's vibe)
Goodness, finally.
I'm finally here.
All right, don't get too excited by the lightings.
Lightings are everything.
Interior design is all about lightings.
It's the lighting zone.
(I should calm down.)
Please.
This one was clearly sold the most.
It's so pretty. How cute.
Gosh, that's pretty too.
It's pretty.
- You're getting another one? - How can a cable be this pretty?
This punk.
I can put a flower in this vase for a nice vibe.
This one's good.
No, you should never get that.
- This is... - The color is too vivid.
That's the highlight.
Every item you got is the highlight.
I think they're inconsistent.
I think you're already done...
with my kind of interior design.
(What did you say?)
It's so pretty. How cute.
(It's been long since he's forgotten Hue-terior.)
This is cute.
This is so pretty. It's driving me crazy.
It's so pretty.
(The final sweep)
Let's get going.
This is how it's done, right?
It's scary.
- How bizarre. - How come he's so greedy...
about everything?
This is how it's done, right?
I don't see anyone purchasing items like me.
- It's hilarious. - I kept turning...
because it was too heavy.
How much will these cost? Darn.
How do I do it?
(It's finally time to pay.)
It'll take you forever to pay for them.
It's like back when I first opened my studio.
Right. You buy things like that...
- when you open a studio. - Right.
(Scanning barcodes as if he'll open a studio)
This is mine too? Wait, whose is this?
Oh, it's not mine. Is it?
Are all these mine?
Hue Park has a great influence on me.
You're suddenly blaming me.
I got lots of Hue-style items.
I think it'll be pretty if you place those items in an empty space.
Kian84, you know a thing or two.
- Painters get each other. - Of course.
You should go to Japan to meet Ito Junji soon.
You're going to steal my idol now?
- Stealing an idol? - I'll tell him I like him more.
Gosh, I'm so tired. How much is it?
What?
It's 1,400 dollars.
It's 1,400 dollars?
- You can rack up points too. - Okay.
- The receipt is so long. - Gosh.
(Surprised)
(A never-ending receipt)
- I bought this many? - It's not like it's a supermarket.
(Slow)
It's "Special Mission Dad's Challenge."
Will all of them fit in your car?
- They will. - They will?
(Managing to move with two carts)
I won't get to try...
- the 70-cent ice cream. - That one's good, though.
- I know. I should've had it. - The ice cream.
(That was satisfying shopping.)
(Humming)
(He excitedly reached home while humming.)
Gosh, this is crazy.
Gosh, it's crazy.
Bringing all of them inside...
- must be a lot of work. - It's really tiring.
(Struggling)
This is crazy.
(Stuff he carried home with great effort)
(Moving them 1 by 1 for now)
Thinking of organizing them... Gosh.
(Putting the cart he used outside)
(Here comes the second cart.)
It's the third cart.
(Pouring in stuff endlessly)
That's a lot.
What's all this?
It looks like you newly moved in.
This is all because of Hue.
Gosh.
It's so hot.
(He's soaked in sweat when he only moved the stuff.)
(Going to the counter with the box in sight)
(He carefully opens it.)
(Pulling out a round lighting)
(He takes his time to read the manual.)
It's really easy. You just need to attach it.
Oh, this one?
(It looks like he's realized something.)
Oh, like this?
Oh, attach it like this?
(Laughing)
It's pretty.
It's simple.
(I should hurry up and turn it on.)
(Click)
(Impressed)
(Yes, this is the vibe I wanted!)
These will take a lot of work.
What's this? What was this again?
Oh, it's the iron piece. What is this?
(Oh, right. I got the Hue-style lighting.)
- That's Hue-style lighting. - Right. I'm familiar with that box.
It's just his style.
This is easy.
- He's become a kid. - I'm almost like a fanatic.
This is how it's done.
That's it. I'm done.
How fast.
Wait.
- Wait, this is... - What is it?
I should've bought a light bulb.
- You didn't get a bulb. - A light bulb.
Oh, you need to get a light bulb separately?
Didn't I get it?
It's really upsetting if you can't turn it on after assembling it.
- Right. You'd want to see it. - I didn't get the light bulb.
Does it have the same bulb as that one?
(Shall I take out the bulb?)
- No! - He broke it!
You wanted to take that out for the new lighting?
(Hyun Moo needs a light bulb for the Hue-style lighting.)
- No! - He broke it!
(Oh, no!)
(Broken into pieces)
The sound is really cruel.
I've not been able to...
assist Hyun Moo for a while.
I think this became a hobby in a strange way.
- What are you talking about? - There's a need...
for us to take care of Hyun Moo.
Are you saying I have no strength in my hands?
I think you keep focusing on other things...
- because you feel empty. - Empty?
I feel so worthless.
That's not it. I'm just worried.
You only used it for ten minutes after assembling it.
Gosh, seriously.
I like simple things.
I really liked it because it was such a pretty ball-shaped lamp.
When I turned it on, it was ecstatic.
It was the color I had in mind.
That exact shade of yellow.
I was so happy, but I broke it right away.
I was five times angrier than when I spilled pistachios.
It was such a shame.
I broke it as soon as I got it.
It lived less than a cicada would.
Those who know a style...
would display the lamp as is in broken pieces.
You'd just walk around even if you bleed.
If Hue walked around while bleeding,
you'd bleed too after saying, "This is it."
"So this is art."
(Taking the bulb out first)
(Sighing)
(Shall I check if it fits?)
He's still trying to fit it.
This one doesn't fit.
This isn't the one. It doesn't fit.
I shouldn't have taken it out.
They all have different socket sizes.
Why did I have to check?
(Upset)
Wait. It's like modern art.
Modern art.
(Displaying the broken piece like he knows a style)
Look. It's like modern art.
It fits perfectly. Right?
(Turning it on)
It's not bad.
It does look pretty.
(Hyun Moo brought something instead of a bulb.)
- What? - What is that?
You bought the exact same one as mine.
It's getting scary now, right?
I'm starting to feel a little bad.
I chose a different color because it was too creepy.
(It's a different color, so don't worry.)
(Transforming into the color Moomoo picked)
I've never seen one in pink.
It's incredible, isn't it?
(Stop right there, Hue-terior.)
Gosh, the color...
Should I have added a yellow one too?
(This isn't the vibe I wanted.)
The white one isn't so nice.
(He's losing the vibe of Hue-terior once again.)
Why did I get the one in white?
I should've chosen a different color.
(He kept assembling the rest while screaming.)
That one?
(His living room is a mess.)
I should assemble that later. First,
I should clear the room.
(Forget about the living room. Let's clear the studio first.)
Gosh, you still have too much stuff.
I think there's no space at all for the new items.
I should clear this part out neatly.
And I'll paint here.
(Moving)
I should move these.
What? There's a lighting too?
What? Oh, it's one that CODE KUNST gave me.
- You bought that from my place. - You had a lighting.
(Convinced by CODE KUNST's pitch 3 years ago,)
(he bought this lighting like fate.)
I had one that was similar.
I had to replace it with the one I broke.
(How lucky. I should use this instead of the broken lamp.)
I almost bought the same one earlier.
I must be crazy.
Goodness.
- Gosh! No! - Gosh! No!
(Crash)
(Dropping)
Seriously...
(Feeling devastated)
(Shaking)
It's really annoying to clean that up.
I'll visit you at home from time to time.
I'm sorry I didn't pay much attention to you.
- Look after me. - Yes.
(Flopping)
Gosh, how many glasses did I break today?
It's crazy.
Why am I starting to feel sorry?
I feel like it's my fault.
It is your fault.
I wouldn't have done something like that...
if I hadn't visited your house.
(Cleaning up the glass bitterly)
(Quickly removing stuff from the studio)
- That's a lot of stuff. - Seriously.
Your studio looks like a store.
What could this be?
What is that?
- What is this? - Crayons?
Oil pastels?
Oh, nice!
Score!
The best kind of interior design is emptiness.
You can only see the space clearly if you empty it.
- He's right. - If I hadn't done that,
I wouldn't have found it until I moved to another place.
- For real. - So,
instead of buying,
if you organize things,
- you'll score items. - That's right!
Actually, what I did better than going to furniture retailer today...
was emptying the room.
Let's get this out. It takes up too much space.
Gosh, these relics.
As for the items I found,
I could put them in the storage,
or I could give them away to those who need them.
(I'll clear it all out.)
- It must be really tiring. - My gosh.
- My gosh. - It must feel refreshing, though.
(After taking everything out, feeling refreshed,)
(the room became empty.)
- The room was quite big. - It's really big.
Pistachio!
(Pistachio!)
(The dizzying memory of pistachios)
Gosh, that only came out now?
At this rate, you must be glad to see it. Right?
Your pet pistachio.
There are so many chairs.
(After removing the old chairs and vacuuming the space...)
(From a room tight with stuff...)
It's become spacious.
The best interior design is emptying.
Excellent.
(Let's see. I'm almost done clearing the room.)
And then...
There are so many chairs.
(Time to place the items he newly bought)
(Out of breath)
It's got a nice vibe.
That's Chunhyang's.
It was pretty when I saw it.
(He spreads it.)
This is a straw mat!
Let's flip it.
Flip it!
(Placing a beige single-seater sofa)
There are just too many chairs.
Is this the vibe I wanted?
But...
(Something's off.)
This isn't right.
It'd suit you if you bind your neck with a shackle with that rug.
Shackle?
(It's perfect.)
Oh, right!
I didn't place lightings.
It's like Yeonnam-dong.
(Placing lighting for a better vibe)
This gives off the vibe.
(Feeling excited,)
(he turns on the light.)
The vibe isn't so bad right now.
The painting and the chair...
Since the cushion is also blue...
I'm seeing your vision now.
(My vision is indeed great.)
CODE KUNST's lighting.
(Next is CODE KUNST's lighting.)
CODE KUNST's lighting is finally revealing its glow.
CODE KUNST's lighting.
(Fiddling)
I'll place it like this.
How tacky! Gosh, CODE KUNST, that punk.
(How tacky! Gosh, CODE KUNST, that punk.)
It was a white light bulb. Darn.
It's not about that.
- You can just change the bulb. - You just need to change the bulb.
He should've told me.
I thought it'd be white for good.
(I didn't know that.)
What would I have done if I hadn't gotten this?
(Putting CODE KUNST's lamp behind, he takes another one.)
This is the highlight. It'll give off the Yeonnam-dong vibe.
- Gosh, this detail! - Which one are you talking about?
- What is it? - Gosh.
- That... - You got those that day?
Yes, I did.
It's to die for!
(It's to die for!)
This is crazy.
Gosh, amazing. It's so pretty!
(Highly satisfied with the combination of wood and green)
This is crazy.
I'll bring this closer and paint as I watch.
All right.
It's not bad, right?
I think it's definitely better now that you emptied it.
- Right? - Yes.
You need to empty it.
What's your honest thought of the room, Hue?
Honestly, seeing the space that he cleared out,
it does look like a studio space for an artist.
(That's it!)
It's not about being right or wrong.
It's a space you want to use based on your feel.
He looks like...
a crazy painter based on that.
It's the highest praise for me.
(Trudging)
(Entering the studio with a canvas in his hand)
Gosh, it's killing me.
Like this. Good.
I should put it like this.
The oil pastels I found today.
I think I found it after three years.
I've never used it. I didn't even know what it was.
It's really hard to use it.
I don't even know how to use it.
It's like a crayon.
I'm using this for the 1st time in 3 years.
(Grabbing the light-blue pastel)
Like this.
Gosh, this is nice. Like this.
(Sitting up properly)
(He starts painting something without hesitation.)
It's a painting dedicated to Hue, who made today possible.
I'm painting it for him.
- A painting dedicated to him? - That's madness.
Actually, Moosquiat...
has become a dealer.
I'm not an artist anymore.
I'd paint something for the bazaar.
I'd paint something when giving away Dubai chewy cookies.
For instance, if I were to make bindaetteok,
I'd paint bindaetteok again with my face on.
(I'd paint bindaetteok again with my face on.)
My pure passion for creation is gone.
I've just become a dealer.
I'm mass-painting like a factory.
They're all the same.
No matter what I paint, it's the same face on DCC.
"Mass-painting like a factory."
When I first began painting with CODE KUNST's face,
the studio wasn't so bad.
I wanted to go in there too.
I reorganized that space again thanks to Hue.
I thought, "Let's go back to when I painted CODE KUNST."
Back to the time when I was pure...
and painted to talk with myself.
It's a tribute to Hue Park.
(The one and only dedication piece of Moosquiat...)
(who's gone back to the beginning mindset)
I wonder how the painting looks...
because it gives off a different feel...
if you paint with oil pastels.
Your painting style changes...
- if your working space changes. - That's right.
Maybe his style of painting will change right away.
(Expectant)
(Rummaging)
(He keeps using different pastels.)
(Coloring the canvas with various colors)
Gosh, Hyun Moo.
- You're like... - You're like a master.
- I mean... - Yes.
- Like Chagall. - It looks like you've gone back...
to the color combinations you used in the beginning.
The master of color.
- Chagall? - Chagall.
- I'm Moogall for today. - You're like Chagall here.
- Chagall? - I'm Moogall.
(A genius painter...)
(who mastered Chagall's painting style after Basquiat's)
(Immersed)
What's with that poster?
"The best sense of humor?"
- "Jun Hyun Moo is the best?" - It's hilarious.
(Hyun Moo is the best.)
(The overflowing self-love befitting a genius painter)
(Slouching)
Gosh, this is really tiring.
(The best sense of humor, the best wit, Jun Hyun Moo is the best!)
(Even in an uncomfortable posture,)
(he continues to paint without a break...)
(like any other painter does.)
(Dumbfounded)
There's passion in my eyes.
You're just as passionate.
I was so proud of myself.
I realized I could change the space in such a short amount of time.
I first went shopping to copy Hue's style,
but ironically, I found myself.
It was a valuable journey.
So I want to say thank you to Hue.
(Although it was awkward because it wasn't a familiar tool,)
(but he painted each stroke with his gratitude toward Hue.)
- He's focused. - He's really focused.
His mouth shows he's focused.
Gosh, that camera movement.
(The night deepens.)
(And his painting deepens.)
- It's like... - My gosh!
(Hue)
Look at his expression.
(Deeply moved)
That's not the Chinese letter I use for "Hue."
This is what you call wit.
I didn't know which Chinese letter you use for Hue,
but...
- It's... - What's with your painting?
- I mean... - I'm scared now.
It's not that. I...
I can't believe I flew for 15 hours just to see that.
It's like a nightmare.
To see that,
- It's a nightmare! - he flew for 15 hours.
- It's dedicated to you. - He flew here for that.
It's my first oil pastel painting style.
Moogall.
It's dedicated to you.
When the scene switched to his painting...
(A lasting impression)
(Looking at it from different angles)
(No matter how many times I look at it, it's satisfying.)
It's meaningful since it is the first oil pastel painting...
from Moosquiat.
And this is...
Jun Hyun Moo napping on a cloud...
while smiling.
Just like Hue's name...
Of course, the Chinese letters must be different.
It felt like taking a break in the skies.
This room will be called Hue's Room from now on.
(It's Hue's Room.)
(Astonished)
(Snickering)
This room will be called Hue's Room from now on.
Today happened thanks to Hue.
And it's a day dedicated to Hue.
(He even dedicates the room to Hue in the end.)
(Placing)
(Hue)
(Displaying it for easy viewing)
How come the painting is so funny?
You used my name for the painting,
but you drew yourself.
(Hue)
It's so pretty.
I love it.
(Leaving the room after feeling fully satisfied)
When will I clean these up? Gosh, I'm so sick of it.
When will I clean these up?
It's a lot of work to clean that up.
(Plopping down)
I'm dying. Gosh, my legs.
Let's clean them up later.
(Hue)
(Dreaming of Becoming Hue)
(Next story)
All right.
(A soccer stadium filled with heavy breathing)
(Someone is commanding the field.)
Wait for it!
(And MINHO is waiting next to him?)
My father is a coach of K League 2.
(MINHO's father, Coach Choi Yun Kyum of Yongin FC)
(MINHO, the son, came to cheer for his father.)
(Smiling widely)
(The fierce coach's heart melted?)
(The coffee truck that MINHO prepared for his father)
(Let's go, Coach Choi Yun Kyum! From his son, MINHO)
(Please be nice to my dad.)
(The son is proud to see people lining up for the truck.)
(Regardless of being grateful,)
(MINHO will have to compete.)
(When it comes to competing, they're not father and son.)
(The Fiery Father and Son stand on the field.)
(Getting competitive even before the match)
(I'm not a professional athlete.)
(I'm not either.)
(He's got his fiery side from his father.)
(Son, I'm the original fiery man.)
(Father, the world has changed.)
(An unpredictable match)
(How would the fiery match end?)
(I didn't show it earlier.)
(But I was a bit sad.)
(They finally talk about what happened that day.)
(My Forever Flame)
(The Little Tiger is back.)
(Roaring)
(The curious lover of greens)
(Member Kim Si Hyeon)
(Walking with excitement)
(I'm in Tongyeong now.)
(My 2nd home)
(Tongyeong)
(Spring greens have arrived early.)
(It's full of rare and fresh ingredients.)
(Whom has she gone to meet as soon as she arrives?)
(A food researcher of Tongyeong, Lee Sang Hee)
(A treasured vegetable garden...)
(overlooking the ocean)
(Amazed)
(Harvesting greens from the garden for the first time in her life)
(The garden is covered with her favorite greens.)
(Totally satisfied with her spring greens foraging)
(Utilizing all of her five senses...)
(to meet new greens)
(Spitting it out)
(I ate weeds.)
(I'm full just like the basket.)
(The real class will begin now.)
(Looking serious in the kitchen)
(Becoming a great chef is a long and difficult journey.)
(She has come to Tongyeong to find the answer to her journey.)
(The harder it gets, the more thorough she becomes.)
(Studying Is the Only Way)